Raju Sharma Dahal

Gauradaha-07-JHAPA | 9817022866 | razzu236@gmail.com

https://github.com/ razzuSharma

https://www.linkedin.com/in/raju-sharma-6a30671b0/

www.rajusarma.com.np

Obsessed with Front End Development. Courteous and enthusiastic in IT and everything around its orbit. I recently began to be fascinated by web development. Interested in research and putting effort in getting a job done in a certain period.

Projects:

BLOG FEB 2023

Created a simple blog displaying web app using React and GraphQL. It displayed

the listing of blogs from the database using react built in hooks.

Tech Used: React, GraphQL, Tailwind CSS

PERSONAL PORTFOLIO AUG 2023

Created a personal portfolio using React and its animation libraries like:

(framer-motion, AOS)

ECOMMERCE WEBSITE AUG 2022

The app basically did crud operations (Delete, Read and Update).

For the API (JSON server was used)

Tech used: Tailwind CSS, Vue JS, JSON Server

B-SERVICE JULY 2022

The app showed the details of the vehicle users, list of vehicles, list of destinations. Third-

party API (Map Box) was used too to create a map layout and for the shortest path too.

Tech used: HTML, BOOTSTRAP, Laravel, JavaScript.

BILLING SOFT MARCH 2021

The application was made for keeping records of the products, supplier details and everything related to the selling and buying system.

Tech used: HTML, BOOTSTRAP, LARAVEL

Soft Skills:

Communication, Problem-Solving, Adaptability, Attention to details, Teamwork, Creativity

Technical Skills:

NextJS, React, Vue JS, Java Script, Laravel, HTML, CSS, GitHub, Linux, GraphQL, Tailwind CSS, Bitbucket, Jira, React-Bootstrap

Experience:

Tegzy 2022-2022 (4 months) Front End Developer

Worked as a software engineer in maintaining and writing reusable components with collaborating with other developers using code maintaining software

Resolved issues and helped break down the bugs in the programs.

BLUE FOX PVT. LTD 2020-2021 (3 months) Front End Developer Intern

Worked as a junior frontend developer intern and helper of the senior developer in keeping the record of projects done. Created front-end UI using bootstrap custom and already existing templates.

Resolved issues and helped break down the bugs in the programs.

Education:

2019-2022 (BACHELORS)

ITAHARI INTERNATIONAL COLLEGE/ BIT

2016-2018(HIGH-SCHOOL)

DAMAK MULTIPLE CAMPUS / +2 SCIENCE

2009-2016(SECONDARY SCHOOL)

KANCHANJUNGA ENGLISH BOARDING SCHOOL/ SLC